https://www.titian.co.uk/privacy-policy?hsLang=en-gb

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy applies to the http://www.titian.co.uk website and to information that Titian Software Ltd stores and processes.
Information We May Collect About You
Information you give us:
This is the information that you provide us, either through online forms or through business interactions; for example, when discussing a sale.
Examples of information stored:
Email address, Name, Employer, Job Title, Phone Number.
Information we collect from you when using our site:
In order to provide you with appropriate marketing material, with your permission, we will store a cookie that allows us to identify you between visits. To remove this cookie, click here (you will be redirected to the homepage and the cookie message will appear again).
If you provide us with further information, such as by entering your email address on the contact page, we may store historical information about your visits.
Examples of information stored:
Pages you have visited on our site, whether you have opened emails that we have sent to you.
Information we receive from other sources:
We receive information from selected Third Parties. In all cases we only use information from these Third Parties if they have asked you and you have given your consent for that information being shared with us. An example would be if you have signed up to a mailing list from a conference at which we were presenting.
Examples of information stored:
Email address, Name, Employer, Job Title.
How the Information Is Used
Marketing Emails
We may use stored information to send you emails for products and services we believe you will be interested in. If you wish not to receive such emails, you can asked to be removed from mailing lists by emailing privacy@titian.co.uk with the text ‘Remove’ in the subject.
Providing Business Services to you and your Employer
In situations where we have a contract to provide software services with your employer, or are in discussions relating to such a contract, we will use information we hold about you to contact you.
Who We Give Information To
We do not sell personal information to any Third Parties. We may give personal information to others in the following situations:
Business Partners
There are some situations where we may share your information with Third Parties. For example, we may hire other companies to send emails on our behalf.
In all cases we will provide only the information required, for example, to send an email we will provide only your email address and name.
Legal Requirements
In certain situations, we may be compelled by public authorities to provide information we store about you. We reserve the right to disclose such information to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or similar legal process served on us.
Where We Store Information
The information may be stored in internal systems at Titian company premises, or securely in selected Third Party service providers. Information stored in Third Party providers may be stored outside the EU and outside the US
How Long We Keep Information
We will keep information about you only as long as we believe is required for its purpose.
Access to the Personal Information We Hold About You
Upon request, we will let you know whether we hold any of your personal information. To request this information please email privacy@titian.co.uk.
If you would like to view the information we hold about you, please email privacy@titian.co.uk and we will provide you a copy of all information we hold in an appropriate format.
If you believe any of the information we hold about you is false, or incorrect please inform us as privacy@titian.co.uk.
All genuine and appropriate emails to privacy@titian.co.uk will be responded to in a reasonable timeframe, and not longer than one month from when the email was received by us.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes.
Contact Us
If you require further information, please contact privacy@titian.co.uk.
Get in touch
Thanks for getting in touch!
Find us on:
Latest from the Blog
Latest from Twitter
Tweets by @TitianSoftware
Keep in touch
© Copyright Titian Software Limited. All Rights Reserved.
